Stephanie Joy d'Obrenan, CHRP, CHRL

Grace Street
Toronto, Ontario
416-605-9432
sdobrenan@gmail.com

PROFILE

A high performing professional with over 9 years of HR experience working in various teams and industries. Trusted advisor to the organization as a strategic business partner providing exceptional service and support by anticipating staff/business needs and proactively identifying opportunities for improvement. Always looking to expand my knowledge and continue to work in a challenging, fun, team oriented environment. Obtained the CHRL designation in 2013 and hold a high degree of knowledge in all key areas of Human Resources.

Leadership Coaching Performance Management Employee Relations Recruitment

People Services Change Management Policy Development Conflict Resolution

Employee Engagement Exit Management Succession Planning Compensation

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

-30 FORENSIC ENGINEERING, TORONTO

October 2015 to PRESENT

Manager, Human Resources

- Manage the full cycle HR function for the firm of 80+ staff
- Sit as a strategic partner on the firm's Executive Leadership and President Council team meetings
- Drove a change in benefits provider for the entire firm, managed changeover from start to finish
- Created and built 30FE's first ever 'Career Development Map'
- Championed and rolled out 30FE's first ever Mentorship Program
- Facilitated and led the organizations learning and development program '30 University'
- Implemented first ever engagement survey, championed change management strategies, followed up by implantation of a micro-engagement tool, 'TINYpulse'
- Chair of both the Wellness and Social Committee corporate programs
- Promote effective coaching and communication to leaders and staff
- Re-vamped the entire onboarding process, maintained management of it

LONGVIEW SYSTEMS, CALGARY

March 2014 to April 2015

HR Business Partner

- Key supporter to leaders and employees in multiple facets of the business
- Working closely with business leaders to efficiently and strategically identify talent resource requirements in support of acquisition, engagement, development and retention of the right people.
 Helping to identify top performers and advise on succession planning and promotions
- Different areas of support include input on career growth, health and disability, employee exit support and performance management
- Provided expert support on all Long View people programs and services including employee guidelines, training and philosophy, compensation models, HSE & company offerings
- Partner with leaders and provide guidance to ensure effective and accurate change management; examples include, employee transfers, re-orgs, progressions, promotions/demotions, relocations, acquisitions

- Advise on employment standards with reference to provincial and federal regulations and legislation.
 Working with legal to identify employee relations risk exposure and facilitate employee exit management
- Advise on compensation and annual salary review program to maintain internal equity and industry competitiveness. Communication and support of the company total compensation and benefits programs to employees

CANADIAN NATURAL RESOURCES LTD., CALGARY

August 2013 to March 2014

Human Resources Advisor, Student Recruitment

- Coordination of engineering and geoscience student recruitment for one of the largest student programs in Canada
- Provide HR support for up to 400 students per year and over 70 Managers
- Assist Managers and VPs with student resource planning and strategic new grad programs
- Coordinate campus events and organize recruitment teams to travel across the country, including attendance of career fairs and on-campus presentations and interviews
- Engage prospective candidates and work to sell and promote the Company
- Facilitate and coordinate interviews, evaluations, and selection of candidates with hiring teams
- Coordinate offer process, onboarding, and the student orientation
- Advise students and managers on matters related to relocation, payroll and compensation, performance, and Company Policy and Procedures
- Provide accurate and comprehensive reporting on student recruitment and staffing data
- Liaise with University and College COOP and Internship program coordinators

CANADIAN NATURAL RESOURCES LTD., CALGARY

February 2011 to July 2013

HR Generalist

- Reported directly to the VP of HR and supported close to 200 employees
- Managed the company's semi-monthly payroll
- Provided hands on day to day support in employee relations, performance management, training and development, full cycle recruitment and onboarding/orientations, compensation and benefits analysis, employee exit management
- Provided full cycle recruitment in hiring engineers, accountants, geologists and technical staff

FORZANI GROUP LTD., CALGARY

January 2009 to July 2011

HR Specialist (Benefits/Disability)

- Worked closely with the Total Rewards team to provide expert guidance in all areas of benefits and disability management
- Case managed over 100 disability, WCB and Maternity claims
- Worked closely with the Forzani's Employee Assistance Program to provide employee referrals and help assist with safe return to work plans

FORZANI GROUP LTD., CALGARY

September 2008 to January 2009

HR Administrative Assistant

- Supported the Human Resources department in multiple areas including recruitment, compensation, employee relations, benefits and disability case management
- Compiled and coordinated the on-boarding process including letters of offer, reference checks, and facilitated the new hire orientation
- Departments main point of contact and projected professional company image while maintaining confidentiality and integrity of information

Yoga Teacher

Taught yoga classes at various corporate locations and yoga studios

EDUCATION	
Saint Mary's University	Halifax, NS
B.A.in Psychology	2008
Certificate in Human Resources Management	2008
Certified Human Resources Leader (CHRL)	2013
Adler Faculty of Professional Coaching	2017- Current

INTERESTS

Yoga: Obtained 400 hours of Yoga teacher training. Traveled to Bali and Iceland to receive training

Sports: Golf, tennis, cycling, hiking

Volunteer: Calgary Human Society, Calgary Drop in Centre, Ride to Conquer Cancer, Habitat for Humanity –

went to Tijuana Mexico and built a house for a less fortunate family